ninjasaga.com 2015-06-07

# Ninja Saga | Game Info

### Privacy Policy

Welcome to Emagist Entertainment, an online game company that specialize in RPG and real-time multiplayer applications that are available through social networking sites (SNS Apps). As a responsible gaming company, we put in our priorities the safety of your personal information shared to us and to protect it from unauthorized disclosure to others. This privacy policy will tell you how your data are collected and used. Please read this privacy policy carefully.

Using the service means that you have the consent to the collection and use of your potential information as discussed in this privacy policy. This policy may be updated from time to time. Notice will not be posted when an update is made; It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy from time to time and if you find any of it unacceptable, you must leave the site and discontinue the use of the service and the site. Your continued use of Emagist services after a change or update has been made to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change or update. 

### Collection of Data

Once you have access on our site or applications using your SNS account we will gather information that you provided on your profile (in accordance with the terms of use of those systems) such as name, gender, date of birth, zip code and e-mail address. We don't generally collect any personal details such as telephone number, street address, etc., except for the billings and payments you made for the game where we store your billing information such as name, street address and phone number.

In game actions are also recorded. Any actions you perform with other players are considered public and your own discretion. Since all our games are played on SNS, it is your responsibility to read and accept the Terms of Use, as well as their Privacy Policy of the certain sites.

We also keep a record on inviting you send into your network. The information associated with it such as email addresses and content are maintained on secure servers. These information are used to inform the person that he or she has been invited to join or play our applications or receive other contents associated with the game.

Finally we collect comprehensive information about the use of the service including information accessing the SNS Apps such as internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages & URLs and the date and time ("Activity Information").

### How We Use Your Information

Personalizing your game visits and experience is one of the few things in which we use your information. We also use your personal information to manage your registration and send you news letters or other information about us.

With regards to third parties such as those who help us in payments, in some cases these third parties may receive your information. We do not sell or rent your personal information. We may, however use certain information about you that is not personally with control and responsibility in its use at all times. Due to contractual obligations with these third parties, the need of sharing information in able to perform the service is needed.

The information you submit to us also help us in displaying targeted advertisements for example; advertisements that are designed according to age group, the location of a user, etc. However we do not provide that information to the advertisers whenever you view an advertisement.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that a website transfers to your computer and recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user. A cookie will contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, contains certain information about your sessions or use of the service.

These cookies help us recognize you as you return to our website. These help us improve our services for cookies help us compile anonymous, collective statistics for us to analyze how users use our site, though you are not identified personally in this way.

### Third-Party Advertising Companies

We use third-party companies to serve advertisements on our site. Cookies are associated with the advertisements to enable the advertiser to track the number of anonymous respondents to the campaign.

Emagist Entertainment does not provide personal information to these third-parties. Emagist Entertainment doesn't have access to cookies that come with these advertisements.

### Security

We have employed appropriate precautions and technical measures to secure your information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, or disclosure. 

### Trademarks

Emagist Logo, game logo and other marks specified on this website are registered trademarks of Emagist Entertainment. All other trademarks not owned by Emagist Entertainment that are visible on this website are properties of their respective owner who may or may not be associated with or supported by Emagist Entertainment.
